Who's that guy?
It's Jolyne Kujo!
Not Lang Rangler!
Did he fail?
Is she getting the disc in his place?
In a few minutes,
her ally will come
to retrieve the disc in the courtyard.
That's the prison chaplain.
What's he doing here?
She knows who I am.
No, she would have attacked me already
if she knew I was her enemy.
Wait! Please, Father!
Please...
Don't set off the alarm!
I don't want to cause any trouble!
What should I do?
It would be easy to knock him out.
It would be nothing at all.
My father's life is at stake.
All I have to do is strike him.
You've already caused trouble.
You unlocked this door
with someone else's work permit.
Where is the holder of that permit,
inmate Lang Rangler?
You don't know me,
and I don't expect
you to believe me.
But I'm not lying to you, Father.
That inmate attacked me.
It was self-defense.
He's unconscious
in one of the laundry baskets.
I must report
this incident to the authorities.
I understand, Father.
I'll be glad to cooperate
once I'm back from the courtyard.
I only need two minutes...
No, just one minute,
Father, please.
I have to get to the courtyard.
That's all I'm asking.
You want me to pretend
I didn't see anything?
This is a matter of life and death.
My father's life and soul depend on it.
A man of God must understand that.
Did you come here alone?
Is anyone else with you?
No, I came alone.
I lied to the chaplain.
But it's for a good cause,
it shouldn't have any consequences.
And I can't tell him about the disc.
Please.
I only need one minute.
Doing someone a favor
means expecting
something in return.
You want people to be kind to you,
that's why you're kind.
Unconditional love doesn't exist.
Unconditional love
is only granted
to those who reach heaven.
You may go.
I'll pretend
I never saw you here.
However, as you suggested,
you'll only have one minute.
Be back at this door
within one minute.
I have no choice.
Someone is hiding behind that jerry can.
If she has an ally,
I'd better not reveal
that I'm Whitesnake's user
by finishing off Jolyne.
The Speedwagon Foundation's agent
told me
that the person
I'm supposed to give the disc to
would identify themselves
as soon as I reached the courtyard.
You...
where's your pass?
You don't have one, it seems.
You're being charged with attempted escape.
What? What happened?
I never considered
setting off the alarm.
I made the right call,
I had a guard posted
to watch the courtyard.
wakatta koto wa amaete naiteru baai janai
S'il y a une chose que je sais, c'est qu'il n'y a pas de temps pour pleurnicher
kibou no ito o tagutte tsukande ugokidasu
J'atteindrai le fil de l'espoir, je l'attraperai et je continuerai mon chemin
harimegurasareru trap and hate kawashiteku
S'étendant tout autour de toi, esquive les pièges et la haine
Okay (Okay) All right (All right)
matta nashi no survival days
Personne ne peut arrêter mes jours de survie
Get away from (Stone Ocean)
Éloigne-toi de (Stone Ocean)
I don't wanna say (There's no chance)
Je ne veux pas dire, (C'est impossible)
Let's get started, count (One, two, three)
C'est parti, compte, (Un, deux, trois)
Take me far away (Fly Stone Free)
Emmène-moi loin, (Vole ! Stone Free)
atashi ga atashi de aru tame ni
Tant que je suis sincère avec moi-même
(Got to be tough)
(Je dois être forte)
Break out (Hey) Mezame yo (Ho)
Explose ! (Hey) Je suis bien debout (Ho)
kinou made no atashi ja irarenai
Je ne veux plus redevenir celle que j'étais avant
Break out (Hey) Donna ni (Ho)
Explose ! (Hey) Peu importe combien (Ho)
michisuu no skill attack saretemo
D'attaques habiles me mettent à mal
genkai wa houkai
Je surpasse mes limites
Give up wa rongai
Hors de question d'abandonner
unmei tenazukeru made
Jusqu'à ce que le destin soit de mon côté...
I don't stop beatin' don't stop beatin'
Je n'arrêterai pas de frapper, n'arrêterai pas de frapper
Don't stop beating 'em up
Je n'arrêterai pas de les frapper
Episode 12   Storm Warning
That was in 1988.
I had befriended a man,
an Egyptian
who claimed to have the power
to stop time.
That day, he suddenly told me...
It may be possible
to reach heaven.
He was young and handsome,
and he carried himself like a man
who had lived for centuries.
At the time, I was 16.
I was still studying.
Don't be so sad.
I'm not talking about death.
The heaven I speak of
concerns the soul.
It's the place our soul goes.
The power of our soul
surely evolves there.
I'm talking about the final form of our souls.
I'm sure you, in particular,
are capable of understanding this.
True happiness lies there.
But to get there,
you must reach heaven.
Happiness isn't achieved
by having the strongest body,
piles of money
or dominating others.
True victory
belongs to those who have seen heaven.
I will do anything to reach that goal.
Can you be more specific?
I've written everything in a notebook.
Come to Egypt sometime.
I'll show you.
I'll need your help
to test my theory.
Sadly,
before I could learn his methods...
the notebook was burned to ashes.
The man who burned it
was Jolyne Kujo's father,
Jotaro Kujo.
Jotaro read the notebook's contents.
Then he sealed its contents for eternity
along with the soul of Dio Brando,
who sought to reach heaven.
I then waited over 20 years
to gain access
to Jotaro Kujo's memory.
The notebook's contents are stored there.
And I finally obtained his memory
along with Star Platinum, which defeated Dio.
Now, Jotaro's body is rotting.
Although his daughter has acted
unpredictably in this prison,
my plan is back on track.
She's been shot!
Someone shot Jolyne!
Who? A guard?
Or did our enemy
get wind of our plan
with Whitesnake hiding somewhere?
Jolyne!
The guard will retrieve Star Platinum.
There's nothing left for me to do here.
I'm heading back to the chapel.
What is that?
A disc.
I remember now,
I was ordered to retrieve this disc.
He also ordered me
to finish off this girl.
But who gave me that order?
I can't remember.
Anyway. I was ordered
to blow her brains out.
It's all over.
There's nothing I can do.
I can't help her anymore.
Your life ends here,
Jolyne Kujo!
Damn it all!
My Stand, Weather Report,
manipulates the weather.
It's what I do best.
Jolyne,
I may be unable to save you,
but I can still protect the disc.
And if you still have the resolve,
you might just make it out alive.
Between 1887 and 1974,
there were over 50 cases of rains
of frogs, fish or sheep
falling from the sky
onto Florida, in the United States.
The cause of these animal rains
is attributed to tornadoes and cyclones.
These frogs are venomous
and they live in the trees
of Central and South America.
The poison produced under their skin
is so toxic
that the natives
dip their arrows in it.
Where are these damn frogs coming from?
They're...
These frogs,
they're poison dart frogs,
known for their toxicity, I believe.
Once their poison enters the body,
it only takes a few seconds
to stop blood circulation
and breathing.
And now they're spraying
their fluids everywhere.
Whitesnake!
That power...
Could it be him?
The one who controls the weather?
Weather Report.
The one with no memory.
Could he be the one hiding
behind the jerry can?
Good Lord,
I can't touch the badge!
These frogs are toxic.
What happened to me?
Was I shot?
What do my wounds look like?
The poison!
It's getting through my fibers!
Someone open this door!
Please!
Stay calm.
Keep your cool.
What do I do in this situation?
Two, three, five.
Stay calm.
Seven.
Prime numbers.
Eleven.
These lonely numbers
only divisible by themselves.
Counting them calms me
and gives me strength.
Twenty-three.
Twenty-eight.
No, 29.
Good Lord.
These amphibians are staining
my 800-dollar pants!
Weather Report is in the laundry room.
That's too far.
I can't stop
this downpour of frogs.
I have to flee.
Forty-one.
Oh, that's right!
The guard in the courtyard.
He's still under my control
thanks to the disc. Where is he?
Guard, can you hear me?
I order you to come back!
Father!
Help me!
Ask God to help me, please!
Forty-three.
Forty-seven.
Fifty-three.
Fifty-nine.
– This poison is super potent.
– Sixty-one.
– Tell God to save me!
– So you can hear me after all.
Give me your badge!
Am I going to make it?
Don't take it out now!
Father!
Sixty-seven.
Sixty-one.
What's going on here?
These frogs...
I'm saved!
Open this door immediately!
Father?
– What's going on?
– How should I know! A tornado?
Hurry up, will you!
Understood.
I'm opening.
These frogs, they...
What are you doing?
A guard lost consciousness on this side.
Quick, open up!
An unconscious guard?
Wait, Father.
I'll get help!
Wait! Where are you going?
Open this door!
Right away!
I understand,
but I need authorization, don't I?
Let me ask my supervisor.
Stay calm. Calm down, Father!
I am very calm.
You're the one...
Seventy-three.
Seventy-nine.
... who's panicking.
You dare abandon me?
I'll be right back, Father!
Whitesnake!
Give me a disc!
I may not have an army to command,
but I can control a frog.
Explode after leaping ten meters.
I command it!
My eyes!
Save me. Father, call for help!
Father,
have mercy!
Eighty-three.
Eighty-nine.
Ninety-seven.
I'm here.
You believe
that if I could get through this door,
I'd heal you immediately,
don't you?
Then come toward my voice.
Father!
Jotaro Kujo's Star Platinum disc.
What do I do with it?
I've taken out Jolyne Kujo,
but I can't leave her alone.
The door is open.
Take me somewhere safe, Father.
Father?
Where are you, Father?
I'm out of string.
I can't protect myself from the poison anymore.
The disc I dropped,
I don't know where it is now!
The rain has stopped.
Where's Jolyne Kujo's corpse?
The disc can't be far.
It was tough,
but my Snake can't
be beaten by frogs.
Find it.
Whitesnake has a range
of 20 meters at most.
It would be a serious problem
if someone saw me here,
but I have no choice.
The spirits of dead criminals
take the form of frogs
and return to this world
to look for companions.
It's an oriental legend
I once heard.
Doesn't it describe
this monstrous scene perfectly?
And the disc is near the body.
Whitesnake.
Search toward the door.
The guard might have had it on him.
It must be in that direction.
Found it!
I've got the disc back.
Thank you very much.
I was waiting for you to find it.
God damn it.
They disgust me.
They're stuck all over me,
I feel like throwing up.
Frogs only release their poison
when they hit the ground.
Unharmed, they're harmless.
I built a carpet
of live frogs
to cushion the fall
of the other frogs
and I waited
for you to find the disc.
Pathetic attempt!
I'm going to kill you, bitch!
He was already here.
I'm talking about the Speedwagon Foundation's
agent.
He wasn't human,
but he was right on time.
He slipped between the frogs
and reached the courtyard.
That pigeon's name is Savage Garden.
A carrier pigeon trained
to bring the disc to its destination.
Whitesnake!
The guard's gun, near the door!
Kill that pigeon!
What a moron, that guard!
He fired all his bullets!
Damn it!
I've won.
Don't underestimate me, bitch!
Nothing has changed.
Even with Star Platinum,
your dear daddy is just a mummy!
He won't even remember his own daughter!
Look! A guard is down!
Don't step on the frogs!
Search the courtyard!
There might be someone out there!
Whatever happens, don't pass out.
Its user must be nearby.
I have to find
Whitesnake's user.
He's the one who has
my father's memory disc.
To find Whitesnake's user,
it's now or never!
Hey! Look out the window!
That's incredible!
It's a miracle!
It has to be a miracle!
But who's going to clean all this up?
The game hasn't turned.
I only took Star Platinum
because of my promise
to avenge my friend Dio.
But it's the memory disc that matters,
and that one, I have it.
Everything is going smoothly.
Only Jotaro's memory
contains the clues
to reach heaven.
A supernatural phenomenon
made it rain frogs
inside the prison.
With all this,
Jolyne's escape attempt
went unnoticed.
The disc containing Star Platinum,
Jotaro Kujo's Stand,
was delivered to the Speedwagon Foundation.
However,
without the memory disc,
Jotaro's soul
won't return to its body.
Même si tu penses que je fais face
Although you think I cope
Ma tête est remplie d'espoir
My head is filled with hope
D'un quelconque endroit autre qu'ici
Of some place other than here
Même si tu penses que je souris
Although you think I smile
Intérieurement et pendant tout ce temps
Inside and all the while
Je m'interroge sur mon destin
I'm wondering about my destiny
Je pense à
I'm thinking about
Toutes les choses
All the things
Que j'aimerais faire
I'd like to do
Dans ma vie
In my life
Je suis un rêveur
I'm a dreamer
Un lointain songeur
A distant dreamer
Rêvant d'espoir
Dreaming far away
Dès à présent
From today
Sports Max,
about this bone,
I want you to do
something to it.
Is that a human bone?
Who does it belong to?
That doesn't concern you.
Let's just say it comes from an old friend.
My dear friend,
Dio's bone.
Kiss of Love and Revenge (1)